jimmyjazz.com 2019-12-22

# Jimmy Jazz Privacy Policy | Jimmy Jazz

**JIMMY JAZZ E-COMMERCE, LLC**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Jimmy Jazz E-Commerce, LLC ("Jimmy Jazz", "we", "our", or "us") respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how and for what purposes we are collecting, processing, and using your Personal Information (as defined below). We pledge that we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your Personal Information and Usage Information (as defined below) will only be used in ways that comply with this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy applies to any web page, email list, onsite data collection, Personal Information and Usage Information collected and/or owned by us, including, but not limited to, our website located at www.jimmyjazz.com/.  This Privacy Policy is in effect no matter the method of collection, including collection through our website and any online features, products, services, and/or programs that we may offer (collectively, the "Website"). Jimmy Jazz will treat any offline collection, uses, and disclosures of your Personal Information consistently with our online privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is not applicable to any web page, social media site, Personal Information or Usage Information collected and/or owned by anyone other than us.

Your use of the Website is also governed by our Terms and Conditions of Use, available at [[www.jimmyjazz.com/terms-and-conditions](http://jimmyjazz.com/terms-and-conditions)].

**Types of Information Collected**

Jimmy Jazz and any third party that we may hire for the purpose of administering, operating, hosting, configuring, designing, maintaining and providing internal support for our Website may collect two types of information when you visit the Website: Personal Information and Usage Information.

**Personal Information:** The types of information that we collect may include, among other things, the following categories of information (collectively, "Personal Information"): 

l contact information (e.g., your name, gender, address, phone number, email address, and month and day of birth); 

l banking information (e.g., bank account and credit/debit card numbers, and billing address); 

l information about why you are visiting the Website; and

l other information specific to you (e.g., your occupation, industry, and personal interests). 

We do not collect any Personal Information from you when you visit our Website unless you choose to provide that information to us. You can browse the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. However, we will automatically collect Usage Information when you browse our Website.

**Usage Information:** The types of usage information that we collect may contain generic information about you when you visit the Website, which may include, among other things, the following categories of information (collectively, "Usage Information"): 

l Internet Protocol (or IP) address or device ID/UDID, protocol and sequence information;

l browser language and type;

l domain name system requests;

l browsing history (including such details as the time spent at a domain, and the time and date of your visit) and number of clicks;

l http headers, and operating system and fingerprinting data; and

l aggregated information.

**How Information Is Collected**

We may collect Personal Information and Usage Information about you from the following sources:

l the correspondence that you and others send to us, including when you complete any online forms or send us an email;

l offline collection, including when we communicate with you by telephone or text;

l information we receive from you through the Website and as a result of your use of our services;

l information about your transactions with, or services performed by, us, our affiliates or nonaffiliated third parties;

l information we receive when you enter our contests or sweepstakes; 

l information we receive from your computer or mobile device;

l information we receive from our affiliates, partners or service providers; and

l information we receive from other sources, as permitted by applicable laws, rules and regulations.

You may be able to sign up to join our mailing list or to receive notifications from us. If you sign up, we may from time to time send you an email or literature with information about one or more of our promotions and general information about us. You can unsubscribe at any time by the means set forth in that communication.

**Cookies**

From time to time, we may use "cookies" to keep track of your visit and your use of the Website and to improve your experience on the Website. A cookie is a small piece of data that your browser stores on your computer's or device's hard drive and is used to collect information, such as identifying those areas of the Website that you have visited in the past in order to enhance your next visit to the Website. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser, but some functionality of the Website may be impaired or not function as intended if you choose not to accept cookies. Each browser is a little different, so look at your Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. You can delete cookies at any time. Our cookies cannot collect any information when you are not accessing the Website. By using our Website, you consent to our use of cookies.

**Use of Collected Information**

Information that we collect may be used for the following primary purposes:

l To provide products and services to you.

l To improve our products and services.

l To personalize your experience on the Website.

l To communicate with you and to inform you about our products and services.

l To help protect the safety and integrity of the Website and our users.

**When Information Is Disclosed and Shared**

We might disclose Personal Information and/or Usage Information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary: 

l To comply with legal processes and applicable law.

l To enforce this Privacy Policy. 

l To take precautions against liability and respond to any claim that any information that you provided violates the rights of a third party.

l To assist government enforcement agencies.

l To protect our rights, property, or the safety or the rights, property, or personal safety of our visitors and the public, which includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction, and, if required by law, disclosing information to U.S. federal and state governmental agencies.

l To investigate potential unauthorized access or misuse of the Website.

l To otherwise enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use and other agreements. 

We may transfer your Personal Information to third parties, including our hosting partners and other trusted third parties who assist us in operating the Website and as necessary for our business purposes. We maintain reasonable safeguards to keep your Personal Information secure. When we provide Personal Information to our affiliates or third party service providers as discussed in this Privacy Policy, we require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy and in a manner that complies with applicable privacy laws. The use of your information by a trusted business partner may be subject to that party's own privacy policy. 

We reserve the right to transfer your Personal Information, as well as any information about or obtained from you, in connection with the merger, sale or other disposition of all or part of our business and/or assets, or in the event of our bankruptcy, reorganization, insolvency, receivership, or an assignment for the benefit of our creditors. You expressly agree and consent to the use and/or transfer of the foregoing information in connection with any of the above described proceedings. We cannot and will not be responsible for any breach of security by any third parties or for any actions of any third parties that receive any of the information that is disclosed to us. 

We will not sell your information to third parties. We will not share your information with third parties who want to send you advertisements or marketing promotions.

We may disclose your Personal Information for any purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information. We may also disclosure your Personal Information with your permission or as directed by you. 

**Security**

Although we may provide certain encryption technologies and use other reasonable precautions to protect your confidential information and provide suitable security, we do not and cannot guarantee or warrant that any information transmitted through the Internet is secure, or that such transmissions are free from delay, interruption, interception or error.

The federal government and technology industry have developed practical tips (available at [www.onguardonline.gov/](http://www.onguardonline.gov/)) to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for the "Verified and Secured" badge located in the website footer, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

**Data Retention**

We will retain and use your Personal Information for as long as is needed for us to be able to provide our products and services to you, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, comply with our internal business practices and standards, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Personal Information is destroyed when it is no longer necessary for these purposes. Our business partners and third-party service providers may have their own data retention policies.

**Information from Children**

The Website is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of thirteen (13). You affirm that you are more than eighteen (18) years of age, or you are an emancipated minor, and are fully able and competent to enter into the terms, conditions, obligations, affirmations, representations, and warranties set forth in this Privacy Policy, and to abide by and comply with this Privacy Policy. In any case, by using the Website, you affirm that you are over the age of thirteen (13), as **THE WEBSITE IS NOT INTENDED FOR CHILDREN UNDER THIRTEEN (13) WHO ARE UNACCOMPANIED BY THEIR PARENT(S) OR LEGAL GUARDIAN(S)**. 

Parents and legal guardians should be aware that this Privacy Policy will govern our use of Personal Information, but also that information that is voluntarily given by children (or others) in email exchanges, bulletin boards, or the like, may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited communications. We encourage all parents and legal guardians to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet. 

**Privacy Outside the Website**

The Website may now or in the future contain various links to other websites. We are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any of those websites. Other than under agreements with certain reputable organizations and companies, and except for third party service providers (as described in this Privacy Policy), we do not share any of the Personal Information that you provide to us with any of the websites to which the Website links. Please check with those websites in order to determine their privacy policies and your rights under them.

We may use the services of third party service providers to process transactions on our behalf. By using our Website, you grant us all necessary rights and consents under applicable laws to disclose to our third party service providers -- or allow those third party service providers to collect, use, retain and disclose to us -- any Personal Information for purposes of providing services to you, including data that we may collect directly from you using cookies or other similar means.

**European Union and Other International Users**

The Services and our products are intended for individuals located in the United States, and your use of our products and services are governed by United States law. We are not targeting or marketing to international users. If you are using the Website or our products or services from outside the United States, please be aware that your Personal Information and/or Usage Information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the Website or our products and services, you consent to your Personal Information and Usage Information being transferred to our facilities and to the facilities of those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

We will only process your Personal Information when we have a legal basis to do so. When we do process your Personal Information, we will do so with your consent as set forth in this Privacy Policy, or because the processing is necessary for the performance of services or to provide products to you, to comply with our legal obligations, to pursue our legitimate interests, or to establish or defend a legal claim.

**Choices with Your Personal Information and Opting Out**

Whether you submit any Personal Information to us is entirely up to you. You are under no obligation to provide any Personal Information to us. However, this information is essential for the provision and quality of some of the services that we offer to you, so we cannot provide you with certain services or provide you with access to certain features if you choose to withhold requested information.

You may choose to prevent us from disclosing or using your Personal Information under certain circumstances ("opt out"). You may opt out of any disclosure or use of your Personal Information for purposes that are incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or for which you subsequently gave authorization by notifying us by one of the methods escribed at the end of this Privacy Policy, or by following the procedures set forth in an electronic communication from us, if applicable. Furthermore, even where your Personal Information is to be disclosed and used in accordance with the purposes stated in this Privacy Policy, you may elect to opt out of such disclosure to and use by a third party that is not acting as our agent. There are some uses from which you cannot opt out, such as to provide products, features or services that you have requested from us. 

Please note that making such requests does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of your content. For example, we may retain the information for our own internal records in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Access and Correction**

Please contact us in the manner described at the end of this Privacy Policy to access your Personal Information in our possession and correct inaccuracies of that information in our records. We ask individuals to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed and amended before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests in limited circumstances, as permitted by applicable laws, rules and regulations. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California's "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide certain personally identifiable information in connection with obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us (once per calendar year) information about the information that we shared (if any) with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared information for the immediately prior calendar year. To obtain this information, please send an email message to [info-request@jimmyjazz.com] with "Request for California Privacy Information" in the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you at your email address in response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements, and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

California residents who use the Website are also entitled to the following consumer rights notice: The Website is owned and/or operated by Jimmy Jazz E-Commerce, LLC. Unless expressly stated, the Website is provided without charge. If you have a question or complaint regarding the services or products provided through the Website, please send an email to customerservice@jimmyjazz.com. You may also contact us by writing to us at 80 Enterprise Avenue South, Secaucus, NJ 07094, or by calling us at 877-307-5299. California residents may reach the Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the California Department of Consumer Affairs by mail at 1625 North Market Blvd., Suite N 112, Sacramento, CA 95834, or by telephone at (916) 445-1254 or (800) 952-5210.

**"Do Not Track" Signals**

Because we may collect your Personal Information from time to time for our own use, we are required to disclose how we respond to "Do Not Track" requests, signals and other similar mechanisms. Note that your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a "Do Not Track" signal to websites and online services that you visit. Like many websites and online services, we currently do not alter our practices when we receive a "Do Not Track" signal from a visitor's browser. To find out more about "Do Not Track," you may wish to visit [www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

**Your Consent to This Privacy Policy**

By accessing and using the Website, you consent to the collection and use of your information (including Personal Information) by us as described above or as we otherwise see fit, in compliance with this Privacy Policy, unless you inform us otherwise by means of the procedure identified below. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy or some part of it, we will make an effort to post those changes on this web page so that you will always be able to understand what information we collect, how we use that information, and under what circumstances we may disclose that information to others. Your use of the Website following our publication of any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms for all previously collected information and information collected from you in the future. We may use comments, information or feedback that you may submit in any manner that we may choose without notice or compensation to you.

If you have any questions or concerns about Jimmy Jazz's Privacy Policy or data processing, if you would like to access your Personal Information, or if you would like opt out of certain sharing, please let us know by sending your comments or requests to:

Jimmy Jazz E-Commerce, LLC 

80 Enterprise Avenue South

Secaucus, NJ 07094 

Phone: 877-307-5299 

Email: [customerservice@jimmyjazz.com](mailto:customerservice@jimmyjazz.com)

Copyright © 2019. Jimmy Jazz E-Commerce, LLC. All Rights Reserved.

Effective as of: July 2019

Last updated: July 2019
